I'm in a room, the lights are dim, the monitors a
steady beep I'm waiting for a bed to open, I'm
trying just to sleep Aubrey's on the vinyl couch
She hasn't left my side I'm starving but the
nurse just said My hands are tied Just me again,
it's midnight now Click, the door swings open
Click, the cuff is on his arm
He's just another false alarm He's trying just
to sleep, but he isn't P.O. And I have got a
promise that this night will be so slow It feels
like just a minute I start to drift away A hazy,
anxious, fitful dream That's begging me to stay
But then the sound, it pulls me back The lock upon
the door The squeak of shoes upon the floor I
can't take anymore It's just me again, it's 2AM
Click, the door swings open
The light is on him He's just another false alarm
He's trying just to sleep But he isn't P.O. And I
have got a promise That this night will be so slow
I'm not a person, I'm a chart A number on a screen
The most annoying endless night that I have ever
seen
Aubrey's jolting on the sofa She's getting zero
sleep This isn't care, this isn't rest The hole
is way too deep Good morning, it is 6am Click, the
lights are on now
Am I still in P.O.? ?
Huh?
Hungry.